{
    "id": "9eac4264cc934463858ab886259c94b3",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. the award for his acts of bravery.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "is deserving",
                "deserves",
                "has deserved"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………… a new generator that saved the company millions.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "designed",
                "designs",
                "has designed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………… candy all the time I was dieting.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "desire",
                "was desiring",
                "desired"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "After the war, the town was a ……………………………… place.",
            "description": "Desolate is the adjective form. Desolated is the past tense of desolate.",
            "answers": [
                "desolate",
                "desolated"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Many coastal towns were ……………………………………. by the hurricane.",
            "description": "Desolated is the past tense of desolate.",
            "answers": [
                "desolate",
                "desolated",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………….. anyone who is cruel to animals.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about our likes, dislikes, preferences etc.",
            "answers": [
                "despise",
                "am despising",
                "despised"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe that our destiny is ………………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "predetermining",
                "predetermined",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the most ……………………………… storm in decades.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "destructive",
                "destructible",
                "destructory"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a desperate criminal on the ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loss",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How can you forgive such ………………………………. behavior?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despicable",
                "destitute",
                "despicible"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A person of such ……………………………. appetite has no place in our community.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "depraved",
                "depraving",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Inflation has ……………………………….. the country’s currency.",
            "description": "Depreciate means lower the value of.",
            "answers": [
                "depreciated",
                "deprecated",
                "depraved"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}